<cyberfit version="1">
    <authors>
        <author id="1">
            <name>Uki</name>
        </author>
    </authors>

    <programs>
        <program active="true" authorId="1" id="1" premium="false">
            <name>Warm-up and Flexibility exercises</name>
            <description>Start with this set before doing any other activity to properly warm up and
                stretch your body.
            </description>
        </program>
        <program active="true" authorId="1" id="2" premium="false">
            <name>Morning Routine</name>
            <description>This set of exercises can be performed anywhere, in the park, in the
                bathroom while morning wash routine, in the gym before training. This set is
                designed to warm up, stretch and condition your body head-to-toe giving you a great
                feeling and a little "taller" posture for the upcoming day. This routine alone will
                keep you tuned up on the days when you are not planning to do any other exercises.
            </description>
        </program>
        <program active="true" authorId="1" id="3" premium="false">
            <name>Outdoor Path</name>
            <description>Map based exercises such as running, jogging, walking, hiking biking.
            </description>
        </program>
        <program active="true" authorId="1" id="4" premium="false">
            <name>Obstacle Course</name>
            <description>Training exercises to prepare for Obstacle Course events such as in
                Military boot camp, Spartan Mud Race. To be able to perform
                these exercises you will have to find a local park with obstacles, as always select
                exercises you want to do as favorites and repeat your runs in the same order so the
                exercises self-sort for you.
            </description>
        </program>
        <program active="true" authorId="1" id="5" premium="false">
            <name>High Intensity, Interval Training</name>
            <description>Set of high intensity exercises you can perform in any clear area such as
                gym floor, home living room, outdoor park.
            </description>
        </program>
        <program active="true" authorId="1" id="6" premium="false">
            <name>Your Own Body Weight</name>
            <description>This set common exercises was selected to allow you to workout
                anywhere using nothing more than your own body weight.
            </description>
        </program>
        <program active="true" authorId="1" id="7" premium="false">
            <name>Your Own Body Weight Bench</name>
            <description>Set of exercises that require only a stable bench (such as in the park) and
                your body weight.
            </description>
        </program>
        <program active="true" authorId="1" id="8" premium="false">
            <name>Floor Lay Down Exercises</name>
            <description>Set of exercises that require a floor space to lay down.
            </description>
        </program>
        <program active="true" authorId="1" id="9" premium="false">
            <name>Gym with Machines</name>
            <description>This set of exercises can be performed in most of the gyms using standard
                machines.
            </description>
        </program>
        <program active="true" authorId="1" id="10" premium="false">
            <name>Gym with Machines</name>
            <description>This set of exercises can be performed in most of the gyms using standard
                machines.
            </description>
        </program>
        <program active="true" authorId="1" id="11" premium="true">
            <name>Dumbbells Weights</name>
            <description>This set of exercises can be performed with a set of dumbbells, or any
                weights you can hold in separate hands, gallon milk jugs full of water, sand, etc.
            </description>
        </program>
        <program active="true" authorId="1" id="12" premium="false">
            <name>Kettle Weights</name>
            <description>This set of exercises can be performed with a set of Kettles, or any
                weights you can hold with both hands, such as gallon milk jug full of water, sand,
                etc.
            </description>
        </program>
    </programs>

    <exercises>
        <exercise active="true" displayOrder="1" trackDistance="true" trackRepetitions="true"
            trackTime="true" trackWeight="true" youtubeId="Z9aXPxgKPl8">
            <assignedPrograms ids="1,2,4" />
        </exercise>
    </exercises>

    <measurement display_order="1" imageResource="">
        <name></name>
        <description></description>
    </measurement>

</cyberfit>